armis.com 2019-08-01

# armis.com Privacy Policy • armis

### Overview

This privacy policy describes how Armis, and associated entities, collect and use personal information that is gathered from our website and customers.

### Website Visitors

Visitors to our website may elect to provide personal information in order to obtain more information about our products and services. Such information may include:

  * Name
  * E-mail Address
  * Phone Number
  * Company Name
  * Country

We collect information from you when you register on our site, fill out a form, use Live Chat, open a Support Ticket or enter information on our site.

### How is Personal Information provided to website used?

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

  * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  * To quickly process your transactions.
  * To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.
  * To follow up with you after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries)

### Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information on Armis website

We may also collect data in a form that, on its own, does not allow us to identify or contact a specific individual. We may use, transfer or disclose non-personal identifiable for any purpose. The following are examples of non-personal information that we collect and how we may use it:

  * When you visit our websites, we may collect technical and navigational information, such as web browser type, Internet protocol address, language, location, time zone, unique device/browser identifier, and URLs requested so that we may better understand visitor behavior and improve our products, services, and content.
  * We may also collect information regarding specific activities that you perform on our websites. This information is used to help us improve the content and usability of our websites. This information is aggregated and we consider aggregated information as non-personal for the purposes of this privacy policy.

**Cookies and Other Technologies on Armis website**

Armis websites, products, services, and content use “cookies” and other technologies such as web beacons and pixel tags. These technologies may be used to keep track of advertisements and to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

We may use this information to analyze trends, administer our website, and to learn about user behavior. If you turn cookies off, some of the features that make your site experience more efficient may not function properly.

We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place. It’s also important to note that we do not allow third-party behavioral tracking

### Cookies and Other Technologies on Armis website

Armis websites, products, services, and content use “cookies” and other technologies such as web beacons and pixel tags. These technologies may be used to keep track of advertisements and to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

We may use this information to analyze trends, administer our website, and to learn about user behavior. If you turn cookies off, some of the features that make your site experience more efficient may not function properly.

We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place. It’s also important to note that we do not allow third-party behavioral tracking

### Armis Customer Deployments

Armis deployments capture device usage in customer environments including running applications, network services, and web services accessed. Customers provide this usage data to Armis, which may contain personal information that includes:

  * IP Addresses
  * Username
  * Mac Addresses
  * Location

Armis uses this information to discover, monitor and provide visibility to all devices in our customer environments. Armis fully identify all managed, unmanaged, and IoT devices – from traditional devices like laptop computers, smart phones to smart devices like TVs, webcams, printers, HVAC systems, medical devices and more. With these devices properly identified Armis is able to take a comprehensive approach to:

  * Provide complete IoT or asset inventory
  * Enable devices to safely connect to the corporate network
  * Secure all outside connections to corporate assets

### Transfer to Third-Parties

Information provided to us or obtained as a result of the use of the website or the Software may be shared with third-party service providers that are engaged to assist us in managing the processes required to provide these services. Any engagement of a third-party service provider will be governed by appropriate contractual requirements prohibiting the use of your information for any purposes beyond those specifically directed by Armis and requiring that they ensure sufficient administrative and technical security mechanisms are in place to prevent your information from being improperly used, disclosed, or accessed.

For individuals located in the European Economic Area (“EEA”) or Switzerland, when transfers to third parties outside of the EEA or Switzerland occur, Armis will put sufficient protections in place to ensure compliance with the applicable legal requirements, such as use of European Union (“EU”) Model Contracts, or language requiring adherence to the EU-U.S. or Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield, General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”), or other such protocols as may be in place from time to time.

We may be required to disclose personal information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security, law enforcement, or data privacy requirements.

### Access to Personal Information

The amount of personal information that we require you to supply in order to use our services will be limited to that which is relevant to supply such services.

You have the right to request access to, withdraw your consent to the use and processing of, and request the correction of inaccuracies or erasure of your information that we maintain about you, subject to our obligations to maintain your information under applicable laws. We may limit or deny requests that interfere with our legitimate interests, or charge reasonable fees for access, except as prohibited by applicable law.

Armis will only store personally identifiable data about you for as long as it’s reasonably required to fulfill the purposes under which it was first provided by you unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

You may make review, update access, correction, or deletion requests by contacting us at [privacy@armis.com](mailto:privacy@armis.com). Where data is controlled by another entity, customers may be redirected to that company’s privacy contact for resolution.

### Protection of Personal Information

To safeguard this information Armis uses technical, administrative and physical data protection controls including firewall barriers, data encryption techniques and authentication procedures, among others.

Armis retains personal information for as long as it is useful in accordance with all applicable privacy and security regulations and all information may be deleted upon request to privacy@armis.com.

### Third-Party Sites and Services

Our websites and content may contain links to other websites. As such, Armis does not endorse and is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these third-party websites. We exercise no control over how your information is stored, maintained or displayed by third parties or on third-party sites.

**Google  
**Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. <https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en>

We have implemented the following:

  * Remarketing via Google Analytics

We do not use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

### CAN SPAM Act

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

We collect your email address in order to:

  * Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions
  * Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.
  * Send you additional information related to your product and/or service
  * Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.

To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:

  * Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.
  * Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.
  * Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.
  * Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
  * Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.
  * Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you do the following:

  * Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.
  * Unsubscribe from this link – <https://response.armis.com/hs/manage-preferences/unsubscribe-simple>

and we will promptly remove you from **ALL** correspondence.

### California Online Privacy Protection Act

With regard to CalOPPA, Armis agrees to the following:

  * Users can visit our site anonymously.
  * This privacy policy is accessible publicly our website.
  * Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’.
  * You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes on this Privacy Policy page.

### Children

The Service is not directed to children. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children. If you, as a parent or guardian, become aware that your child has provided us with Personal Information without your consent, please contact us. If we become aware that a user is under the age of 13 and has provided us with Personal Information without verifiable parental consent, we will delete such information from our files.

### Notifications

Should a data breach occur, you will be notified via email according to regulatory requirements.

We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

### Privacy Changes and Questions

Armis may update its Privacy policy from time to time. When we change the policy in a material way, a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated Privacy Policy.

Last Updated:  **July 10, 2019**
